Photographs Archival Collection 6038 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- "Return to" (Box 17, Folder 19)
- ILR Events (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Public Affairs - San Francisco & LA (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Public Affairs (Sept.-Oct. 1995) - 9/15/1995 -- 1-10 Building Construction Panel - 9/23/1995; Homecoming - Oct. 12/1995 - Auditorium (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Saparta Groat (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Salvatore, Student Awardee - 9/1996 (Dewey Neild, Photographer) (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Unlabeled Photos (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Unlabeled photos (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Gormley Miller - Diesel-Electric Locomotive Models (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Group photos outside of ILR (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Photo/Slides - given to Archives by Helen Hamilton (retired employee) (Box 18, Folder 5)
  26 slides
- Class of 1984 Slides (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Ithaca Fire Fighters - 1973 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous oversize photographs (Box 19, Folder 1)
  31 photos, sorted out of the 'misc. photos' box that had been over the mapcase
- Miscellaneous oversize photographs (Box 20, Folder 1)
  36 photos, sorted out of the 'misc. photos' box that had been over the mapcase